In this video we are going to learn
prerequisites,
tools and resources for the course.
Let me start with the prerequisites.
This course assumes that
you have very basic programming skills whether in python,
.net or nodejs.
Familiarity with the APIs will also help since we will
explore how to interact with the LLM APIs and agents.
Mainly we will design interface software architectures
with integration of the AI agents,
so it is good to know the basics of the software architectures.
Next,
the course slides.
Each lecture comes with the detailed slides
summarizing the key points and concepts,
and these slides are available for download in this lecture resources section
that you can see on the slide picture
how you can download from lecture resources from the Udemy.
I highly encourage you to download and review
them as you progress through the course.
And finally,
a very important request from my side
as you go through the course,
if you are finding the content valuable and it is helping you learn,
please consider taking a moment to leave a command and a 5 star review.
Your positive reviews and constructive feedback
are incredibly motivating and important.
They encourage me to continue creating more in-depth courses like this one.